yieldbuild.com 2013-12-10

# YieldBuild

> This privacy policy was last modified on July 31, 2012.

YieldBuild, Inc. (â€œYieldBuild,â€ â€œwe,â€ or â€œusâ€) knows that you care how information about you is used and shared. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by YieldBuild when you use YieldBuild.com and related services (the â€œServiceâ€), how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this policy are defined in our End User License Agreement at [https://yieldbuild.com/pages/eula.](https://yieldbuild.com/pages/eula)

### Information We Collect

**User-Provided Information** : You provide us information about yourself, such as your name and e-mail address, when you register with the Service. If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our responses.

**Cookies Information** : When you visit YieldBuild.com, we may send one or more cookies â€“ a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters â€“ to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets YieldBuild help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie does not collect personal information about you. YieldBuild uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browserâ€™s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. You also can manage your cookies via the Network Advertising Initiative at [http://www.networkadvertising.org.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

**Log File Information** : Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you register with or view our site, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website or click on any ads. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (â€œIPâ€) address, browser type, date and time information, computer and connection information, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the sites, ad data, web log data, and other such information from your interaction with our sites, services, content and advertising.

**Clear Gifs Information** : When you use the Service, we may employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. No personally identifiable information from your YieldBuild account is collected using these clear gifs. In addition, we may also use clear gifs inÂ HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and make YieldBuild better for our users.

### How We Use Your Information

We use the personal information you submit to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service (including to enroll You as a publisher with Advertisers).

Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose for posting to the Service, if applicable, becomes available to the public. If you remove such content, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored it.

By providing YieldBuild your email address you consent to our using the email address to send you Service-related notices, including any notices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail. You may not opt out of Service-related e-mails or click tracking. We may also use your email address to send you other messages, such as newsletters, changes to features of the Service, or special offers. If you do not want to receive such email messages, you may opt out by sending an email message to support@YieldBuild.com with the word â€œNo emailâ€ in the subject field. Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates, improvements, or offers.

YieldBuild may use certain information about you without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as analyzing how the Service is used, diagnosing service or technical problems, maintaining security, producing industry reports on advertising trends, and personalizing advertisements and promotions.

YieldBuild reserves the right, but has no obligation, to monitor any content you post on the Service. YieldBuild has the right to remove any such information or material for any reason or no reason, including without limitation, if in its sole opinion, such information or material violates, or may violate, any applicable law or our End User License Agreement or to protect or defend its rights or property or those of any third party. YieldBuild also reserves the right to remove information upon the request of any third party.

We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site; (b) provide custom, personalized advertising, content, and information; ©monitor the effectiveness of our service; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and traffic; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company orÂ ISP; and (f) help you efficiently access your information after you sign in.

### How We Share Your Information

**Personally Identifiable Information** : YieldBuild will not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to others. YieldBuild may share your personally identifiable information with third parties solely for the purpose of providing services to you. If we do this, such third partiesâ€™ use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of YieldBuild (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers).

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution.

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, YieldBuild will not disclose personal information to any third party unless required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law, comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates, or investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities; (b) to enforce our [End User License Agreement](https://yieldbuild.com/pages/eula), take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, or to protect the security or integrity of our site; and © to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of YieldBuild, our users or others.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information** : We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to provide the Service and help them understand the usage patterns for certain YieldBuild services. We reserve the right to retain ad delivery and reporting data as long as may be necessary for accounting and audit purposes.

YieldBuild allows third-party ad servers or ad networks to serve advertisements, or may itself serve advertisements, through the Service to YieldBuildâ€™s customersâ€™ websites. These ad servers or ad networks use technology to send advertisements and links directly to the end userâ€™s browser. They automatically receive the end userâ€™s IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content.

YieldBuild does not provide any personally identifiable information to these ad servers. However, please note that if an advertiser asks YieldBuild to show an advertisement to a certain audience and an end user responds to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that the end user fits the description of the audience they are trying to reach.

The end user should consult the respective privacy policies of third-party ad servers or ad networks. The YieldBuild privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, third-party advertisers. Any solicitation of personal information through such advertisements is strictly between the advertiser and end user.

### How We Protect Your Information

YieldBuild uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to YieldBuild and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, YieldBuild makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to your email communications from YieldBuild, at all times.

**Compromise of Personal Information**  
In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, YieldBuild will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

**Your Choices About Your Information**

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through YieldBuild, in which case YieldBuild may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your account information and email preferences at any time by logging in to your account. You can review and correct the information about you that YieldBuild keeps on file by contacting us directly at support@YieldBuild.com.

**Children’s Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, YieldBuild does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to YieldBuild or on the Service. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at support@YieldBuild.com.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including those that have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web siteâ€™s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Notification Procedures**

It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to you via email notice, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on our website, as determined by YieldBuild in its sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our website to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at [support@YieldBuild.com](mailto:support@YieldBuild.com), or send mail to:

YieldBuild, Inc.  
95 Minna St., 3rd Floor  
San Francisco, CA 94105

### Recent Changes To The YieldBuild Privacy Policy.

July 31, 2012: We have added third-party ad network enrollment information.
